<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Product PDF="">
	<Frame ID="1">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Optional mechanical tailgate" SubPic1="1_0_330_4107.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>A mechanical tailgate allows for additional payload capacity of up to 59,525 lbs. (27 000 kg).</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Auto-lube system" SubPic1="1_1_330_4160.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>The auto-lube system continuously greases all lubrication points through a central distribution block, greatly reducing daily maintenance requirements and increasing machine reliability.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Flip-forward hood" SubPic1="1_2_330_4151.jpg" SubPic2="1_2_330_4154.jpg" SubPic3="1_2_330_4156.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Hydraulic, flip-forward hood provides easy access to maintenance points, engine, valves and pumps.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="2">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="New lighting package" SubPic1="2_0_330_04-12.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>New lighting package with lamps in bumper and at top of cab provides direct illumination of  the job site.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Long, sloping hood" SubPic1="2_1_330_4117.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>A long, sloping hood gives the operator improved all-around job site visibility.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Remotely controlled mirrors" SubPic1="2_2_330_4117.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Heated, remotely controlled side mirrors are optional equipment on the 330 ADT. </p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="3">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Swing-out fenders" SubPic1="3_0_330_4173.jpg" SubPic2="3_0_330_4174.jpg" SubPic3="3_0_330_4176.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Swing-out fenders on both sides of the truck offer high level of accessibility to maintenance/service zones.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Sliding window" SubPic1="3_1_330_4084.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>A sliding cab window improves operator comfort through additional ventilation.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="4">
		<!-- Move dot at hinge -->
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Longitudinal difflock" SubPic1="4_0_330_4084.JPG" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Longitudinal difflock permits operation of the vehicle in four- or six-wheel drive for safe, efficient operation in changing terrain and driving conditions. Vehicle is in two-wheel drive when difflock is not engaged.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Sharp skow angle" SubPic1="4_1_330_4084.JPG" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>A sharp skow angle lets material discharge easily from the load body.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="5">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Spacious cab" SubPic1="5_0_300-001-01.jpg" SubPic2="5_0_300-002-07.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>A spacious cab is designed for operator comfort and ease of use with ergonomically designed controls positioned within the operator's easy reach, status lights readily visible, an adjustable steering console and a suspension seat that adjusts to the operator. Air conditioning is standard.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Pressure test ports" SubPic1="5_1_330_4150.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Pressure test ports conveniently are grouped together and are easy to reach for quicker, more accurate diagnostic checks.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Easy cab entry" SubPic1="5_2_330_4128.JPG" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Steps to the cab are designed with easy entry/exit in mind.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="6">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Limited-slip axles" SubPic1="6_0_330_4165.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Limited-slip axles deliver power to where it’s needed most, from the wheel that is slipping to the wheel that is gripping.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Wide frame retained" SubPic1="6_1_330_4131.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Case articulated dump trucks retain a wide frame and lower dump body, which creates a lower center of gravity and exceptional stability.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Optional rear-view camera" SubPic1="6_2_330_4133.jpg" SubPic2="6_2_00106.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>For added safety and enhanced productivity, an optional closed-circuit camera and monitor lets the operator clearly see objects behind the vehicle. </p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="7">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Axle oscillation" SubPic1="7_0_330_4162.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Vehicle moves easily over rough terrain with axle oscillation.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Tandem walking beam" SubPic1="7_1_330_4163.jpg" SubPic2="7_1_330_4164.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>The tandem walking beam is mounted directly off the frame for added strength and durability.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Dual-element air filter" SubPic1="7_2_330-004-10.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[A dual-element air filter screens out more dust and debris. The filter can be replaced from ground level.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="8">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Dump cylinders inside frame" SubPic1="8_0_330_4146.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Housing the dump cylinders inside the truck's frame gives added stability to the vehicle and better protects the cylinders from the elements than if they were mounted outside the frame.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Dual roller carrier bearings" SubPic1="8_1_330_4149.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Dual roller carrier bearings in the oscillation joint provide extended life and reliability.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Tier 2 engine" SubPic1="8_2_330-004-07.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Tier 2 certified engine delivers net 300 hp (224 kW) with reduced emissions and greater performance and efficiency. With charged air-to-air engine cooling, air entering the intake manifold is cooler. Because cool air is denser than warm air, more air enters the combustion chamber, providing a more efficient and cleaner burn. </p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
</Product>
