<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Product PDF="">
	<Frame ID="1">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Redesigned linkage" SubPic1="1_0_721Dxt.4280.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Redesigned linkage for improved sightlines and increased productivity.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Improved bucket rollback" SubPic1="1_1_721Dxt.4283.jpg" SubPic2="1_1_721Dxt.4284.jpg" SubPic3="1_1_721Dxt.4286.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Increased bucket rollback improves productivity through maximum material retention. Level lift is achieved throughout the entire lift/dump cycle.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="2">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="New lighting package" SubPic1="2_0_lightsTop.jpg" SubPic2="2_0_lightsBottom.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>New lighting package with lamps mounted high on cab and at operator level improves illumination to forward work zone.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Better line of sight to attachments " SubPic1="2_1_721Dxt.4237.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Redesign of attachment area provides improved operator view of hydraulic coupler, bucket, or other attachments, such as fork. This results in improved productivity.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Rapid-fill bucket design " SubPic1="2_2_721Dxt.4398.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Bucket penetrates material easily for heaped buckets every time.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="3">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Angled steps " SubPic1="3_0_721Dxt.4433.jpg" SubPic2="3_0_721Dxt.4434.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Angled steps make climbing into the cab easier for reduced operator fatigue.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Low-profile hoses " SubPic1="3_1_721Dxt.4274.jpg" SubPic2="3_1_721Dxt.4275.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Low-profile routing of hoses to conform closer to loader arms further improves operator's forward visibility.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Limited-slip axle" SubPic1="3_2_721Dxt.4268.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Limited-slip axles automatically transfer power from the wheel that is slipping to the wheel that is gripping.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="4">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Spacious cab with ergonomic controls" SubPic1="4_0_controlPanel.jpg" SubPic2="4_0_joysticks.jpg" SubPic3="4_0_pedals.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Cab features low interior noise levels; standard, low-effort joystick control for all boom functions; forward/neutral/reverse quick shuttle switch for easy loader operation; flat glass to eliminate distortion and is easily replaced; uninterrupted sightline to right-hand control switches; adjustable steering console; dual brake pedals, and optional Air Ride seat and air conditioning.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Improved view of latching pins " SubPic1="4_1_721Dxt.4241.jpg" SubPic2="4_1_721Dxt.4244.jpg" SubPic3="4_1_721Dxt.4242.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Latching pins for hydraulic coupler now easier to see from operator's seat.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Outboard wet disc brakes" SubPic1="4_2_721Dxt.4266.jpg" SubPic2="4_2_721Dxt.4267.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Outboard planetary and wet disc brakes provide ease of serviceability and machine stability because the weight is outside the frame rather than inside.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Remote drains" SubPic1="4_3_721Dxt.4254.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Remote drains accessible from ground level, allow controlled removal of hydraulic oil, engine oil and coolant by attaching drain hoses.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="4" SubTitle="Power Shift transmission" SubPic1="4_4_721Dxt.4368.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Power Shift transmission automatically matches the gear to the application. The transmission also can be operated in the manual mode.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="5">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Reduced-profile counterweight" SubPic1="5_0_721Dxt.4258.jpg" SubPic2="5_0_721Dxt.4440.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Reduced-profile counterweight swings within standard turning radius of tires and provides better stabilization during carry operations.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Electronically controlled hood lift" SubPic1="5_1_721Dxt.4335.jpg" SubPic2="5_1_721Dxt.4337.jpg" SubPic3="5_1_721Dxt.4339.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>One-piece, electronically controlled flip-up hood allows easy access to all daily maintenance checkpoints. </p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="6">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Optional exterior mirrors" SubPic1="6_0_721Dxt.4343.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Optional exterior mirrors improve operator visibility and safety. Interior cab mirrors are standard equipment.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Tail lights set in hood" SubPic1="6_1_721Dxt.4257.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Tail lights set in hood, above counterweight, for improved visibility on the jobsite.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Contoured hood" SubPic1="6_2_721Dxt_4440.jpg" SubPic2="6_2_721Dxt_4344.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Contoured hood provides industry-leading rear visibility.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="7">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="EPA Tier 2 certified engine" SubPic1="7_0_721Dxt.4247.jpg" SubPic2="7_0_721Dxt.4251.jpg" SubPic3="7_0_721Dxt.4253.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Tier II certified engine produces more power on demand with lower emissions. Filters easily accessible from ground level; mounted vertically for easy spin on/off. Sight guages provide easy view of fluid levels in transmission and hydraulic tank.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Mid-mount cooling module" SubPic1="7_1_721Dxt.4249.jpg" SubPic2="7_1_721Dxt.4250.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Cube-shaped, mid-mount cooling module constantly supplies clean air to all coolers, thereby increasing cooling efficiency, reducing fluid breakdown and extending component life. Raised panel allows easy access to coolers. Reversible, hydraulically driven fan purges debris from<br />all coolers.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="8">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Steering cylinders mounted high" SubPic1="8_0_721Dxt.4261.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Steering cylinders mounted high in chassis to protect against debris and extend component life.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Optional Ride Control" SubPic1="8_1_721Dxt_4435.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Improved productivity with optional Ride Control. This increases material retention, reduces shock load on the machine, and increases operator comfort.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Lube for Life driveline" SubPic1="8_2_721Dxt.4263.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Lube for Life driveline exemplifies Case commitment to reduce level of maintenance needed on all its construction machines.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
</Product>
