<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- edited with XMLSPY v5 U (http://www.xmlspy.com) by Asuka (Asuka) -->
<!-- 721D Wheel Loader -->
<Product PDF="">
	<Frame ID="1">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Pilot-operated hydraulics" SubPic1="1_0_smarthydraulics.jpg" SubPic2="1_0_pilot1.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Pilot-operated hydraulics and a load-sensing, pressure-compensated system provide optimum flow and power to all hydraulic functions as needed, improving performance.</p><p>This improves operation when more than one function is being used simultaneously and it improves fuel economy. More power also is available to the wheels when hydraulics are not being used.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Loader linkage options" SubPic1="1_1_loaderconfig1.jpg" SubPic2="1_1_loaderconfig2.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>The 721D comes in standard Z-bar linkage or a tool-carrier configuration for maximum versatility. These wheel loaders deliver superior breakout forces up to 32,960 pounds (14 950 kg) to move more material per hour.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Larger buckets fill faster" SubPic1="1_2_01106.JPG" SubPic2="1_2_Image01.jpg" SubPic3="1_2_bucketfill.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Bucket capacities on the 721D have been increased to between 3.0 and 3.5 cubic yards (2.30 to 2.70 cubic meters), and the boiling characteristics improved. The 721D bucket is designed to penetrate into the pile easily and transition material to the back of the bucket quickly. D Series buckets fill rapidly and to heaped capacity to move more tons per hour.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Single-lever controls" SubPic1="1_3_721Cab05.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Single-lever controls provide easy operation of the loader, transmission downshift, and return-to-dig and return-to-travel features. An F-N-R quick shuttle switch improves efficiency for fast cycle times. </p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="2">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Mid-mount cooling module" SubPic1="2_0_cool1.JPG" SubPic2="2_0_Cool.JPG" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>D Series wheel loaders feature a Case-exclusive, cube-shaped mid-mount cooling module that constantly supplies clean ambient air to all coolers, increasing cooling efficiency, extending component life and reducing fluid breakdown.</p> <p>With no stacked coolers, the mid-mount module keeps debris from plugging between coolers and makes Case D Series machines the wheel loaders of choice for any application working in conditions with airborne debris.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Electric flip-up hood" SubPic1="2_1_flipuphood.JPG" SubPic2="2_1_Service119.jpg" SubPic3="2_1_Service1_32.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Electric flip-up hood provides convenient access to ground level maintenance checks, helping make the D Series best in class for ease of maintenance and service.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Limited-slip differentials" SubPic1="2_2_limitedslip.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Limited-slip differentials on both front and rear axles maximize tractive effort and minimize tire wear. This feature transfers power from the wheel that is slipping to the one that is gripping, retaining power when pushing material or crowding a pile in wet or muddy conditions.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Ground-level remote drains" SubPic1="2_3_Service101.jpg" SubPic2="2_3_Service102.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Ground-level remote drains for hydraulic oil, engine oil and coolant make changing fluids quick, easy and environmentally friendly.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="3">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Angled steps" SubPic1="3_0_angledsteps.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>New angled steps ease entry to and exit from the cab.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Tier II-certified Case engines" SubPic1="3_1_Service120.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>The new Case engine in D Series wheel loaders delivers cleaner, more efficient performance thanks to electronic engine controls and charge-air cooling. The new design helps the engines meet the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency’s Tier II certification for lower emissions.</p><p>Charged air cooling delivers cooled air to the engine intake manifold. Charging of the engine with cooled, denser air results in cleaner combustion and better fuel economy. The Auto Power feature on the 721D is delivered automatically when the engine senses the need, increasing net horsepower from 170 to 184 (127 to 137 kW). A big advantage of having Auto Power is that the machine will match the horsepower to the application automatically.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Rear counterweight" SubPic1="3_2_counterwt1.jpg" SubPic2="3_2_counterwt2.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Dig and lift stability is augmented by an integrated, bumper-style rear counterweight that houses recessed tail lights, stop lights, backup lights and tie-down brackets.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Side access panels" SubPic1="3_3_sidepanel1.jpg" SubPic2="3_3_sidepanel2.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Straight-lift access panels on right and left sides aid access to daily check points and the mid-mount cooling module.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="4" SubTitle="Electronic information center" SubPic1="3_4_infocenter1.jpg" SubPic2="3_4_infocenter2.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>A convenient electronic information center provides easy-to-read displays showing machine diagnostics, speed, transmission modes, gear, turn signals, engine coolant temperature and oil pressure and hydraulic oil temperature. The information center also includes indicator lights for low coolant, brake pressure, parking brake, filters and other functions.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="4">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Sloping hood aids visibility" SubPic1="4_0_slopehood1.jpg" SubPic2="4_0_slopehood2.jpg" SubPic3="4_0_slopehood3.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>The view to the rear is enhanced by the clean, modern design of the contoured rear hood.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Hydraulic-driven, reversible fan" SubPic1="4_1_blowout.swf" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>A hydraulically controlled fan within the cooling module can be reversed to dispel airborne debris from the module within seconds. The machine stays on the job site without being moved to a cleaning station. The fan is controlled by a switch inside the cab for operator convenience. This innovative feature greatly improves uptime and performance in dusty conditions.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="5">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Ergonomic, high-visibility cab" SubPic1="5_0_Cab02.jpg" SubPic2="5_0_cabview2.jpg" SubPic3="5_0_cabview.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>The ergonomically designed cab has extensive glass for superior sight lines and panoramic views.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Ride Control" SubPic1="5_1_01108.jpg" SubPic2="5_1_01502.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Optional Ride Control allows loader arms to act as shock absorbers to cushion load and minimize bucket spill.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Attachment versatility" SubPic1="5_2_attach1.jpg" SubPic2="5_2_attach2.jpg" SubPic3="5_2_attach3.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Attachments available to mount on D Series wheel loaders include forks, jib booms, scrap grapple, 4-In-1 and side-dump buckets. General-purpose buckets can be equipped with either a bolt-on edge or teeth. A hydraulic quick coupler is optional, allowing the operator to change attachments quickly to improve machine versatility and utilization.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Low-mounted engine for stability" SubPic1="5_3_521D2.jpg" SubPic2="5_3_00406.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>The mid-mount cooling module allows the engine to be mounted low and at the rear of the machine for extra stability.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
</Product>
