<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Product PDF="">
	<Frame ID="1">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Loader Geometry" SubPic1="1_0_animation.swf" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[The 445CT offers power reach vertical lift for operations involving lifting and reaching, while the 450CT has a power cycle radial arm configuration for high-production digging and faster cycle times.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Powerful Engine" SubPic1="1_1_400Series-00102.jpg" SubPic2="1_1_400Series-03106.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[Case Compact Track Loaders feature the new large-displacement, high-torque, long-life Case Family III engine. It's Tier 2 certified and provides quiet, smooth power for productive operation. The engine on the 445CT is naturally aspirated, while the 450CT engine is turbocharged. The 445CT delivers 74 net horsepower (55.2 kW) with a lift capacity of 3,500 pounds (1 588 kg). The 450CT (not shown) offers 82 net horsepower with a lift capacity of 3,858 lbs. (1 750 kg).]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Undercarriage Adapted from Big Machines" SubPic1="1_2_400CTSeries-00102.jpg" SubPic2="1_2_400CTSeries-00202.jpg" SubPic3="1_2_400CTSeries-00204.jpg"><![CDATA[The undercarriage design technology is adapted from that of the midsize dozers and excavators in the Case product Line. The result is a long life machine, a comfortable ride, and a simplicity that makes maintenance easy. The undercarriage features a tapered frame cover combined with steel mud scrapers to help keep water, mud and debris from damaging the track area. This design assures durability while reducing operating costs.]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="2">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Low Effort Servo-Hydrostatic Controls" SubPic1="2_0_400Series-02705.jpg" SubPic2="2_0_400Series-02706.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[The new Case Compact Track Loaders are equipped with low-effort servo-hydrostatic controls that reduce fatigue during operation and ensure day-long comfort. ]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Factory Ready Cab" SubPic1="2_1_400Series-02103.jpg" SubPic2="2_1_400Series-02707.jpg" SubPic3="2_1_400Series-02709.jpg"><![CDATA[A factory-ready cab offers comfort and visibility. Optional air conditioning is available.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Full-Array of Attachments" SubPic1="2_2_445CT-02808.jpg" SubPic2="2_2_445-03109.jpg" SubPic3="2_2_445CT-01506.jpg"><![CDATA[A full array of attachments is available for the Case Compact Track Loaders including augers, brooms, backhoes, dozer blades, stump grinders, landscape rakes, tree shears, tree spades, scarifiers, snowblowers, forks, buckets and more.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Better Visibility" SubPic1="2_3_400Series-03004.jpg" SubPic2="2_3_400Series-02506.jpg" SubPic3="2_3_445CT-02608.jpg"><![CDATA[Positioning the instrumentation on the right upright post results in outstanding visibility to the bucket. ]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="3">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Rigid Mount for Stability" SubPic1="3_0_400CTSeries-00207.jpg" SubPic2="3_0_400CTSeries-00302.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[A rigid mount delivers stability and low operating cost.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Easy Adjust Track Tension" SubPic1="3_1_400CTSeries-00304.jpg" SubPic2="3_1_400CTSeries-00104.jpg" SubPic3="3_1_400CTSeries-00101.jpg"><![CDATA[Track tension is easily adjusted with a grease gun. ]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Case Exclusive 10-Second No Tools Tilting ROPS/Cab" SubPic1="3_2_445CT-03006.jpg" SubPic2="3_2_445CT-03008.jpg" SubPic3="3_2_400CTSeries-00112.jpg"><![CDATA[Serviceability is facilitated with the “no tools,” tilting ROPS/cab.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Self Leveling" SubPic1="3_3_445CT-03206.jpg" SubPic2="3_3_445CT-03207.jpg" SubPic3="3_3_445CT-03308.jpg"><![CDATA[The Case 450CT comes standard with mechanical self leveling in the up and down cycles. The 445CT, with the power reach vertical lift arm, offers optional hydraulic self leveling for raising the bucket.]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="4">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Dual Cone Face Seals" SubPic1="NA" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[Dual-cone face seals provide a reliable, long-lasting seal for a significant decrease in operating costs over the life of the machine.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="2-Speed Operation" SubPic1="4_1_400Series-01002.jpg" SubPic2="4_1_445CT-04801.jpg" SubPic3="4_1_445CT-04706.jpg"><![CDATA[Optional two-speed operation accelerates the 450CT to 7.5 mph and the 445CT to 8 mph. This allows for quicker cycle times and movement around the job site. The trigger-style switch is comfortably positioned for easy use.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Optional Ride Control" SubPic1="4_2_445CT-02404.jpg" SubPic2="4_2_445CT-04601.jpg" SubPic3="4_2_445CT-04608.jpg"><![CDATA[An optional Ride Control™ feature provides improved material retention while reducing shock on the machine and operator fatigue.]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="5">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Tapered Track Frame" SubPic1="5_0_400CTSeries-00207.jpg" SubPic2="5_0_400CTSeries-00208.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[The tapered track frame helps keep the track clean.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Alternating Track Lugs" SubPic1="5_1_400CTSeries-00203.jpg" SubPic2="5_1_400CTSeries-00105.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[Alternating track lugs make for a smoother ride and better traction.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Thick, Heavy-Duty Chassis" SubPic1="NA" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[The Case Compact Track Loaders feature a heavy-duty, one-piece welded steel chassis that can stand up to the pressure of daily work. ]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Quick Access to Service Points" SubPic1="5_3_445-00506.jpg" SubPic2="5_3_400Series-02608.jpg" SubPic3="5_3_445-00301.jpg"><![CDATA[Checking the fuel fill, oil fill, engine oil and air cleaner is easily accomplished by lifting the rear hood.]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="6">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="500-Hour Oil Change" SubPic1="6_0_445-00404.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[The Case Compact Track Loaders feature a long service interval for engine oil changes — 500 hours — which lowers operating costs.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Balanced Cooling" SubPic1="NA" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[The cooling system provides balanced cooling to both the engine and hydraulics. Auxiliary hydraulics swing out for high flow options that contribute to outstanding reliability.]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="7">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Convenient Coolant Acess" SubPic1="7_0_400CTSeries-00111.jpg" SubPic2="7_0_400Series-02608.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[A quick check of the coolant and hydraulic oil levels can be performed by opening the swing out door.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="95-Amp Alternator" SubPic1="NA" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[In addition to the Tier 2 engine, the Case Compact Track Loaders feature a 95-amp alternator for reliable starts. ]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Radial Piston Drive Motor" SubPic1="7_2_450CT-00810.jpg" SubPic2="7_2_450CT-02008.jpg" SubPic3="7_2_450CT-00804.jpg"><![CDATA[A radial piston-drive motor with a planetary final drive delivers a high-tractive effort and four times longer life.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Triple Flange Rollers" SubPic1="NA" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[Triple flange rollers deliver maximum track life and work with single-flange front and rear idlers to help prevent de-tracking, especially on side slopes. ]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="8">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Grid Heater" SubPic1="NA" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[A grid heater option is available for cold-weather starting.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Undercarriage Boosts Productivity" SubPic1="8_1_445CT-03703.jpg" SubPic2="8_1_445CT-02408.jpg" SubPic3="8_1_445CT-01404.jpg"><![CDATA[The undercarriage design adds about one ton to the Case Compact Track Loaders vs. Case Skid Steers with equivalent engines. The added weight boosts breakout force and tipping load.  ]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Track Components Protected" SubPic1="8_2_400CTSeries-00208.jpg" SubPic2="8_2_400CTSeries-00207.jpg" SubPic3="8_2_400CTSeries-00103.jpg"><![CDATA[Track components are protected by a large spring mounted to the front idler.]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
</Product>
