<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- edited with XMLSPY v5 U (http://www.xmlspy.com) by Asuka (Asuka) -->
<Product PDF="">
	<Frame ID="1">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Operator Platform" SubPic1="1_0_131RT16.jpg" SubPic2="1_0_CX3101.jpg" SubPic3="1_0_rops46.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>ROPS/FOPS certified four-post canopy provides operator protection against machine rollover and falling objects. For complete operator comfort, a cab configuration with high-visibility glass is available for CX compact excavators.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Hydraulic Backfill Blade" SubPic1="1_1_CX3602.jpg" SubPic2="1_1_dozerblade.jpg" SubPic3="1_1_127_RT16.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Hydraulically controlled backfill blade adds to machine stability and is available for light dozing work. CX compact excavators excel at digging a trench and laying pipe, then backfilling with the blade. The CX14 model has collapsible blade ends that allow the blade to retract for traveling through gates or narrow openings.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Durable Rubber Tracks" SubPic1="1_2_track.jpg" SubPic2="1_2_151_RT16.jpg" SubPic3="1_2_152_RT16.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Durable rubber tracks are standard to prevent damage to asphalt, concrete or other surfaces. Short-pitch rubber used on the tracks results in minimal travel vibration and noise.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Undercarriage technology" SubPic1="1_3_44RT16.jpg" SubPic2="1_3_under91.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Undercarriage technology is comparable to that found on large excavators. Heavy-duty travel motors provide excellent ground drive traction, which is particularly beneficial when climbing slopes. Heavy plate guards prevent damage to the hydraulic motor piping.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="2">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Oil and gas cover" SubPic1="2_0_196.jpg" SubPic2="2_0_8RT16.jpg" SubPic3="2_0_031_RT16.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>The cover to the oil and gas tanks is made of an ultra-high molecular weight composite that is both durable and light weight. A breather on the oil tank prevents cavitation, rust and corrosion, and extends the life of hydraulic devices. </p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Fingertip controls" SubPic1="2_1_203RT8.jpg" SubPic2="2_1_fingertip1.jpg" SubPic3="2_1_fingertip2.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Fingertip control on the left joystick actuates both the swing and swing boom function. Moving the left control from side to side swings the upper frame of the excavator.</p>  ]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Two-speed travel button" SubPic1="2_2_travel_levers.jpg" SubPic2="2_2_CONTROLSRT16.jpg" SubPic3="2_2_TRAVEL150.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Two-speed travel button is located on right travel lever. High speed is available for traveling across straight, level terrain and low speed where greater traction is required. </p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Center-swing boom" SubPic1="2_3_21.jpg" SubPic2="2_3_37RT16.jpg" SubPic3="2_3_48RT16.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Center-swing design allows the operator to dig directly alongside fixed objects. This parallel-digging feature makes these units ideal for working in tight spaces, whether a fenced-in backyard, or a cramped downtown construction site.</p><p>CX14 - 80 degrees left / 50 degrees right<br>CX25 - 58 degrees left / 65 degrees right<br>CX31 - 70 degrees left / 60 degrees right<br>CX36 - 70 degrees left / 60 degrees right<br>CX47 - 73 degrees left / 58 degrees right</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="3">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Auxiliary hydraulics and plumbing" SubPic1="3_0_38RT16.jpg" SubPic2="3_0_78RT16.jpg" SubPic3="3_0_HYDRT8.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Auxiliary hydraulics and plumbing offer bidirectional-hydraulic flow to the arms to provide power for a range of attachments. </p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Heavy plate guard" SubPic1="3_2_126RT16.jpg" SubPic2="3_2_47RT16.jpg" SubPic3="3_2_PLATE02.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Heavy plate guard protects hydraulic cylinder for backfill blade from blade overflow or damage from objects falling from the bucket. The hydraulic cylinder for the blade comes with joint-type piping for easy replacement. </p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="4">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Buckets &amp; Attachments" SubPic1="4_0_HAMMER.jpg" SubPic2="4_0_bucket1.jpg" SubPic3="4_0_BUCKETATTACH07.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>A wide range of attachments such as hammers, augers and bucket thumbs give the operator more options and extend the machines’ capabilities.</p><p>CX14, 0.78 - 1.3 cubic ft / 0.022 - 0.036 cubic m<br>CX25, 1.4 - 3.0 cubic ft / 0.039 - 0.85 cubic m<br>CX31, 2.13 - 4.25 cubic ft / 0.060 - 0.12 cubic m<br>CX36, 2.13 - 6.6 cubic ft / 0.060 - 0.186 cubic m<br>CX47, 3.0 - 9.8 cubic ft / 0.085 - 0.277 cubic m</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Swing-boom" SubPic1="4_1_cx36_04.jpg" SubPic2="4_1_CX3105.jpg" SubPic3="4_1_cx36_05.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Swing-boom mechanism allows the front attachment to swing to the right and left by an amount that varies by model. The swing-boom bracket and turning mechanism is heavy-duty cast steel, specifically designed for durability and the intended use of auxiliary attachments.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Zero tail swing" SubPic1="4_2_71RT16.jpg" SubPic2="4_2_91RT8.jpg" SubPic3="4_2_ZEROTAIL.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Zero tail swing provides peace of mind when operating the machine in confined spaces where fences, buildings and other stationary objects otherwise would limit operation. With zero tail swing, counterweight does not extend beyond the tracks at any point in 360 degrees of rotation. </p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="5">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Parallel digging" SubPic1="5_0_CX3603.jpg" SubPic2="5_0_parallel1.jpg" SubPic3="5_0_parallel2.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Parallel digging with center-swing boom allows the operator to dig alongside fixed objects, making it ideal for tight spaces such as cramped downtown construction sites and fenced-in suburban backyards.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Swing-out access panels" SubPic1="5_1_40RT16.jpg" SubPic2="5_1_access1.jpg" SubPic3="5_1_access2.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Swing-out access panels give easy access to daily check points and service areas. The operator seat on the CX14 flips up to provide easy access to engine and components.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Quiet, reliable engines" SubPic1="5_2_039.jpg" SubPic2="5_2_newengine.jpg" SubPic3="5_2_quiet.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Engines in the CX series are quiet and reliable. Noise levels from 78 to 82 decibels allow these machines to work in urban and residential areas with little disruption.</p> ]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="6">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Easily accessible engine components" SubPic1="6_0_023.jpg" SubPic2="6_0_component1.jpg" SubPic3="6_0_component2.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Engine components are readily accessible via rear panel that swings outward. Ground-level access to all service points makes for easy daily service and improved uptime.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Travel &amp; Traction" SubPic1="6_1_046RT16.jpg" SubPic2="6_1_cx3601.jpg" SubPic3="6_1_traction.jpg"><![CDATA[<p>Heavy-duty travel motors provide excellent ground drive traction, which is necessary when climbing slopes. </p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="One-touch deceleration" SubPic1="6_2_134RT16.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>One-touch engine deceleration allows the operator to lower engine RPMs to idle speeds minimizing fuel consumption and exhaust</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="7">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Select your control-pattern " SubPic1="7_0_36RT16.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>Control-pattern selection feature allows the operator to choose the operating pattern of the joysticks: SAE or tractor loader/backhoe. When operating in SAE pattern, right joystick controls the boom up/down function while the left controls the arm in/out function. Functions are reversed in the tractor loader backhoe pattern.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="CX Engines" SubPic1="7_1_230RT8.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>The engines on the CX Compacts feature a “pusher” style fan that provides efficient cooling and simplifies maintenance by reducing accumulation of debris in heat exchanges.</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="8">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Work lights" SubPic1="8_0_53RT16.jpg" SubPic2="8_0_LIGHT132.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>A working light on the arm is standard.</p>]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Bucket Widths" SubPic1="8_1_CX060.jpg" SubPic2="8_1_CX3610.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[<p>An assortment of bucket widths are available. Maximum bucket capacity is 9.8 ft³ (0.277 m³). Maximum dig depth is 11 ft 11 in (3.63 m).</p>]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
</Product>
