<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- edited with XMLSPY v2004 rel. 2 U (http://www.xmlspy.com) -->
<Product PDF="">
	<Frame ID="1">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Tall front tires" SubPic1="1_0_MSeries-05803.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[Tall, 12.5 X 18 front tires add  ground clearance and flotation capability to the 580 Super M + model.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Larger operator cab" SubPic1="1_1_MSeries-02401.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[A larger cab on the 580 Super M + gives the operator more leg room and more space  to turn around.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Transmission-mounted hydraulic pump" SubPic1="1_2_MSeries-04103.jpg" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[The transmission-mounted hydraulic pump makes it easy to service the belt on the engine with no spline maintenance required.]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="2">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="93-inch loader bucket" SubPic1="2_0_MSeries-05707.jpg" SubPic2="2_0_MSeries-03803.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[The new 93-inch bucket on Super M + models offers loader capacity of up to 6,182 pounds (8.165 kg).]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Increased torque rise" SubPic1="2_1_MSeries-02303.jpg" SubPic2="2_1_MSeries-02104.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[Larger engine displacement delivers increase torque rise for faster loader and backhoe cycle times.]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="3">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Tier 2 emissions certified" SubPic1="3_0_MSeries-03709.jpg" SubPic2="3_0_MSeries-03003.jpg" SubPic3="3_0_MSeries-03007.jpg"><![CDATA[Tier 2 emissions-certified engines from Case are quieter and smoother running  and deliver increased peak torque for improved lugging ability. ]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="4">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Limited-slip front differential" SubPic1="NA" SubPic2="NA" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[The limited-slip front differential on Super M + models delivers greater traction, making it ideal for working in uneven and soft ground conditions.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="In-cab pattern change" SubPic1="4_1_MSeries-01004.jpg" SubPic2="4_1_MSeries-01009.jpg" SubPic3="4_1_MSeries-01102.jpg"><![CDATA[With the in-cab switchable pattern change on models with Pilot Control, an operator easily can switch between backhoe and excavator control preference for increased productivity. ]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Extendahoe controller" SubPic1="4_2_MSeries-01003.jpg" SubPic2="4_2_MSeries-04306.jpg" SubPic3="4_2_MSeries-01202.jpg"><![CDATA[The exclusive, thumb-proportional controlled Extendahoe on models with Pilot Control allows for easy, relaxed operation and precise control.]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="5">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Larger engine displacement" SubPic1="5_0_MSeries-02109.jpg" SubPic2="5_0_MSeries-03801.jpg" SubPic3="5_0_MSeries-02207.jpg"><![CDATA[More cubic inches gives the engine greater lugging capacity.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Low-effort stabilizer control" SubPic1="5_1_MSeries-01201.jpg" SubPic2="5_1_MSeries-01206.jpg" SubPic3="5_1_MSeries-01408.jpg"><![CDATA[An electric, fingertip control on models with Pilot Control means the stabilizers are operated with little effort.]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="6">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Large rear tires" SubPic1="6_0_MSeries-05803.jpg" SubPic2="6_0_MSeries-05501.jpg" SubPic3="6_0_MSeries-05509.jpg"><![CDATA[Large 21L X 24 rear tires are another reason why the 580 Super M + has extra flotation.]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Infinitely variable backhoe control" SubPic1="6_1_MSeries-02407.jpg" SubPic2="6_1_MSeries-01909.jpg" SubPic3="6_1_MSeries-01107.jpg"><![CDATA[For the ultimate in operator comfort and control, M Series 2 loader/backhoes are available with Pilot Control as an option. To accommodate operator preferences, controls are infinitely variable in the fore/ aft and lateral positions .]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Optional auto-up stabilizer" SubPic1="6_2_580M-02404.jpg" SubPic2="6_2_590SM-03201.jpg" SubPic3="6_2_MSeries-02706.jpg"><![CDATA[An optional, auto-up stabilizer on models with Pilot Control allows the operator to raise the stabilizers while swiveling the seat to the loader position for fast and easy backhoe-to-travel operation.]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
	<Frame ID="7">
		<Nav ID="0" SubTitle="Less frequent oil changes" SubPic1="7_0_MSeries-03501.jpg" SubPic2="7_0_MSeries-02208.jpg" SubPic3="NA"><![CDATA[With oil change intervals now at 500 hours, less time is spent on routine maintenance while more time can be devoted to working on the job site.  ]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="1" SubTitle="Larger diameter boom cylinder" SubPic1="7_1_MSeries-04509.jpg" SubPic2="7_1_MSeries-03405.jpg" SubPic3="7_1_MSeries-02609.jpg"><![CDATA[The 580 Super M features a larger diameter boom cylinder that generates 10 percent greater craning power for lifting and placing heavy objects, such as manholes. ]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="2" SubTitle="Auto shift transmission" SubPic1="7_2_MSeries-07103.jpg" SubPic2="7_2_MSeries-04205.jpg" SubPic3="7_2_MSeries-01205.jpg"><![CDATA[On Power-Shift equipped machines, select the maximum travel speed desired. Then, the transmission will automatically shift up or down to match travel speed to load requirements. ]]></Nav>
		<Nav ID="3" SubTitle="Comfortable wrist rests" SubPic1="7_3_MSeries-01106.jpg" SubPic2="7_3_MSeries-01804.jpg" SubPic3="7_3_MSeries-00905.jpg"><![CDATA[Wrist rests that are height adjustable are a Case exclusive feature designed with maximum operator comfort in mind.  ]]></Nav>
	</Frame>
</Product>
