<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Main pic must be 458x310. Sub pics must be 90x68 -->
<Product MainPic="Cover1.jpg">

	<!-- ==============================Story 0========================= -->
	<Story ID="0" Title="Putzmeister Introduces New TK 25 Hydraulic Trailer Pump" SubPic1="0_TK25.jpg" SubPic2="" SubPic3="" SubPic4="" SubPicCaption1="Putzmeister introduced the new TK 25 hydraulic trailer pump to fill a special market niche. It handles higher volume grout work because its &quot;hydraulic valve&quot; allows the pump to go in reverse." SubPicCaption2="" SubPicCaption3="" SubPicCaption4="" WordDoc="0_TK25.doc" PDFDoc="0_CP3118US.pdf"><![CDATA[<p>STURTEVANT, Wis. (March XX, 2003) — To fill a special market niche, Putzmeister introduced a new 24-cubic-yard-an-hour &quot;hydraulic&quot; trailer pump called the Thom-Katt® TK 25. It was officially unveiled at this year&apos;s World of Concrete.</p>

<p>The new unit is ideal for pumping concrete for commercial on-grade slabs and upper decks. It also conveniently handles block fill, stem walls, patios and other residential projects.</p>

<p>The TK 25 attains up to a maximum 24-cubic-yard output, an 1000-psi concrete pressure, and is powered by a dependable 46 horsepower Deutz diesel engine. Because it is hydraulic driven, like the company’s larger Thom-Katt models, the TK 25 has the ability to pump in both forward and reverse.</p>

<p>Other significant features include a proven reliable S-valve to pump today’s harsher mixes more efficiently. The S-valve can be adjusted at the outlet end of the hopper, which is unique to this model within the Thom-Katt product range. A hinged hopper section provides easier access for the replacement of wear parts. In addition, the unit’s lightweight design allows for towing by a standard pickup truck for convenient on- and off-road travel.</p>

<p>Dave Rudin, national sales manager for Thom-Katts, said, “The TK 25 is an ideal pump to handle higher volume grout work because its ‘hydraulic valve’ allows the pump to go in reverse. You can’t do that with a ‘ball valve’ pump since it utilizes balls and seats.”</p>

<p>For more details, contact Putzmeister direct at (800) 884-7210 or (262) 886-3200.</p>

<p>Putzmeister America is one of the world's leading heavy equipment manufacturers, specializing in concrete and material placing equipment. As market leaders in technology and innovation, Putzmeister offers a complete line of truck-mounted concrete boom pumps, separate placing booms, truck-mounted telescopic conveyors, and trailer-mounted concrete pumps.</p>

<p>In addition, the company provides a wide range of mortar, grout, shotcrete, plaster and fireproofing pumps and mixers, industrial pumps, as well as tunneling and mining equipment. The company achieved international ISO 9001 quality certification in 1998.</p>]]></Story>

	<!-- ==============================Story 1========================= -->
	<Story ID="1" Title="Modern Art Takes Advantage of Modern Equipment" SubPic1="1_ConcretePour5.jpg" SubPic2="1_Night6a.jpg" SubPic3="" SubPic4="" SubPicCaption1="With the help of four state-of-the-art Putzmeister boom pumps, a huge 1.5-acre &quot;reflections&quot; pool was placed next to the newly constructed Modern Art Museum of Fort Worth, Texas." SubPicCaption2="The completed Modern Art Museum is shown with its new &quot;reflections&quot; pond. The pond was pumped by O&apos;Brien Concrete Pumping using Putzmeister equipment. (Note to editor: this caption must contain the photo credit line. Photo property of Modern Art Museum of Fort Worth. Night View. Photography by David Woo.)" SubPicCaption3="" SubPicCaption4="" WordDoc="1_modernart.doc" PDFDoc=""><![CDATA[<p>STURTEVANT, Wis. (March 31, 2003) — With the help of four state-of-the-art Putzmeister concrete boom pumps, a huge 1.5-acre “reflections” pool was placed next to the newly constructed Modern Art Museum in Fort Worth, Texas. The unusual pond was designed to reflect the glass and steel galleries of the new building’s unique architecture created by Japanese architect Tadao Ando.</p>

<p>With limited access to the site, the four Putzmeister boom pumps placed 1,400 cubic yards of concrete within 12 hours. Extreme care had to be taken to avoid both roof overhangs and the 40-foot-high transparent walls of glass surrounding three sides of the L-shaped building where the pond was created. In addition, mixer trucks were prohibited from driving over the rebar.</p>

<p>Dean Norvell of O’Brien Concrete Pumping, Inc., of Keller, Texas, who supplied the pumping services, said, “This was the biggest pool I’d ever seen. And because of the limited site conditions, we needed a 90-meter pump. But since no such machine exists, we were forced to pump from one unit to the next to get the required reach and keep the mixers off the rebar.”</p>

<p>As a result, a 36-Meter and a 28Z-Meter were allowed to drive atop the rebar and set up only once. Then the 36-Meter pumped to another 36-Meter positioned inside the grade, and the 52Z-Meter pumped to a 28Z-Meter in the same manner.</p>

<p>As the pour progressed to the outer edges, the pumps were moved from inside the grade and the rebar reset. Then the two 36-Meter Putzmeister pumps finished the job.</p>

<p>The pour started on a Sunday night around 8 p.m. to avoid traffic congestion, ensure concrete availability and prevent cold joints. Beall Concrete of Fort Worth continuously dispatched the concrete from two nearby batch plants. Consequently, concrete was placed at a rate of over 100 yards an hour.</p>

<p>After the successful pour, the pond was flooded with water. As a result, the new Modern’s setting on 11 landscaped acres with the large reflecting pond at the building’s edge will provide a restful complement to the building’s architectural strength by day. By night, with the building walls bathed in an even glow of light, the transparent glass and steel galleries will appear as large lanterns floating on and reflected in the pond.</p>

<p>The construction of the new 153,000-square-foot Modern Art Museum in Texas began in September 1999 with the official opening of the $60 million project on December 14, 2002. The museum is noted for its vast collection of postwar art, featuring approximately 2,600 works of art. The facility boasts 53,000 square feet of gallery space, making it second in size only to the Museum of Modern Art in New York.</p>

<p>###<br/>JOB SPECS:<br/>Owner:  MPA Foundation, a non-profit entity created to facilitate the redevelopment of the property<br/>Architect:  Tadao Ando Architect & Associates – Osaka, Japan<br/>General contractor:  Linbeck Construction Group – Fort Worth, Texas<br/>Concrete contractor: Foundations by Rangel – San Antonio<br/>Pumping contractor:  O’Brien Concrete Pumping – Keller, Texas <br/>Ready-mix supplier:  Beall Concrete – Fort Worth, Texas<br/>Equipment:  Putzmeister 52Z-Meter, 36-Meter (2) and 28Z-Meter concrete boom pumps</p>]]></Story>

</Product>
