<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!-- Main pic must be 458x310. Sub pics must be 90x68 -->
<Product>
	<!-- ==============================Story 0========================= -->
	<Story ID="0" Title="The Polaris Professional Series 2x4, 4x4 and 6x6 UTVs" SubPic1="0_050_RT8.jpg" SubPic2="0_085_RT8.jpg" SubPic3="0_103_RT8.jpg" SubPic4="0_118_RT8.jpg" SubPic5="" SubPic6="" WordDoc="0_UTVs.doc" PDFDoc=""><![CDATA[<p><i>(MINNEAPOLIS, MN - March 21, 2002)</i> - Unmatched towing capacity and more standard features than other vehicles. Loaded with standard features that are added options on most other vehicles, the Polaris Professional Series 2x4, 4x4 and 6x6 Utility Task Vehicles (UTVs) quickly, smoothly and safely move workers and cargo around any work environment.</p>

<p>The 4x4 and 6x6 are equipped with a 4-valve, 4-stroke, liquid-cooled Polaris 500 engine and the 2x4 features the Polaris&#8217; 425 engine. Low/super-low transmission gearing and on-demand true 4-wheel drive team to provide unbeatable traction across even the toughest terrain.</p>
   
<p>In addition to great traction, Polaris Professional Series UTVs can pull more than any other off-road utility vehicles in its class. The 4x4 and 6x6 have an unmatched towing capacity of 1500 lbs. and the 2x4 can tow 1,400 lbs. A rustproof cargo box can hold up to an additional half-ton payload and the Polaris UTVs&#8217; electric dump box lift makes loading and unloading easier.</p>
  
<p>Even under a heavy load the UTVs foot-actuated 4-wheel hydraulic disc brakes provide these Workmobiles with outstanding stopping power. Polaris offers braided stainless steel brake cables that don&#8217;t rust, freeze or fade like competitive cable-type brakes.</p>
  
<p>Up front, independent MacPherson strut suspension provides 6.25 inches of travel for a smooth ride and easy steering. The dual-shock rear swing-arm suspension with 6.25 inches of travel absorbs bumps while keeping cargo safely in place.</p>
  
<p>Among the standard features on Polaris&#8217; UTVs are reverse alarm, electric dump box lift, headrests, cup holders, quartz halogen headlights and a 12-volt accessory outlet. A full windshield, winch kit, turf tires, mud and EMT Run Flat tires, a plow blade, roof, side and cargo box covers, outdoor cover, enclosed steel cab and rear cab frame protection are among the available accessories.</p>
  
<p>The UTVs are part of the new Polaris Professional Series Workmobiles. This line of commercial vehicles and equipment includes Polaris&#8217; ATV Pro 4x4, Light Utility Hauler 6x6, and ASL 300 All-Surface Loader along with pumps and generators.</p>
  
<p><b>About Polaris </b></p>

<p>Polaris designs, engineers, manufactures and markets snowmobiles, all-terrain vehicles, Victory motorcycles, personal watercraft, and  the Polaris RANGER for recreational and utility use. Polaris is the largest snowmobile manufacturer in the world, and one of the largest U.S. manufacturers of ATVs and personal watercraft. Polaris enhances the riding experience with a complete line of Pure Polaris apparel, accessories, and parts available at Polaris dealerships.</p>
  
<p>Consumers can also purchase apparel and accessories around the clock online at www.purepolaris.com. Polaris Industries Inc. trades on  the New York Stock Exchange and Pacific Stock Exchange under the symbol &quot;PII,&quot; and the company is included in the S&amp;P SmallCap 600 stock price index.</p>]]></Story>
	<!-- ==============================Story 1========================= -->
	<Story ID="1" Title="The Polaris Professional Series ATV Pro and LUH 6x6" SubPic1="1_149_RT8.jpg" SubPic2="1_228_RT8.jpg" SubPic3="1_264_RT8.jpg" SubPic4="1_285_RT8.jpg" SubPic5="" SubPic6="" WordDoc="1_LUH6x6.doc" PDFDoc=""><![CDATA[<p><i>(MINNEAPOLIS, MN - March 21, 2002)</i> - Only true 6-wheel drive vehicle boldly goes where no vehicles have gone before. Built to provide the individual worker with access to the slickest, slimiest, and most treacherous job sites; the Polaris Professional Series ATV Pro 4x4 and Light Utility Hauler 6x6 don&#8217;t have to take the path of least resistance to reach their destination.</p>

<p>The only true 6-wheel drive utility vehicle on the market, the Light Utility Hauler 6x6 offers on-demand 6-wheel shaft drive with a simple flip of a thumb switch. Polaris&#8217; ATV Pro features full-time 4-wheel drive and 6-ply Goodyear Rawhide tires with the capability to navigate rough or muddy terrain.</p>
  
<p>A powerful 4-valve, 4-stroke, liquid-cooled Polaris 500 engine delivers outstanding torque and enables the ATV Pro to tow up to 1,225 pounds. And although powerful, the Polaris Professional Series ATV Pro and Light Utility Hauler 6x6 are the first and only ATVs equipped with tamper-proof technology that limits the vehicle&#8217;s top speed to 25 M.P.H. -- and keeps the worksite safe.</p>
  
<p>Both vehicles have single lever activated, 4-wheel hydraulic disc brakes and an automatic EBS Engine Braking System that provide quick stopping and greater vehicle control.</p>
  
<p>Up front, independent MacPherson strut suspension with 6.7 inches of travel provides a smooth ride and easy steering. In the back, it&#8217;s Polaris&#8217; renowned progressive rate swing arm rear suspension that softens even the biggest bumps by delivering 7.1 inches of travel.</p>

<p>The ATV Pro and Light Utility Hauler 6x6 are built on reinforced Gen IV chassis designed to handle years of sustained effort. Both vehicles are part of the new Polaris Professional Series Workmobiles. This line of commercial vehicles and equipment also includes Polaris&#8217; 2x4, 4x4 and 6x6 Utility Task Vehicles and the ASL 300 All-Surface Loader along with pumps, generators and accessories.</p>

<p><b>About Polaris</b></p>

<p>Polaris designs, engineers, manufactures and markets snowmobiles, all-terrain vehicles, Victory motorcycles, personal watercraft, and the Polaris RANGER for recreational and utility use. Polaris is the largest snowmobile manufacturer in the world, and one of the largest U.S. manufacturers of ATVs and personal watercraft. Polaris enhances the riding experience with a complete line of Pure Polaris apparel, accessories, and parts available at Polaris dealerships.</p>
  
<p>Consumers can also purchase apparel and accessories around the clock online at www.purepolaris.com. Polaris Industries Inc. trades on the New York Stock Exchange and Pacific Stock Exchange under the symbol &quot;PII,&quot; and the company is included in the S&amp;P SmallCap 600 stock price index.</p>]]></Story>
</Product>
